So now we're here, in the here and now, and motherfuckers don't got no tools.
Not only do they not have the tools, they don't even have the mindset needed to fight for themselves.
They mad at me for talking about Barack Obama being a centrist, retired politician, and that somehow being okay.
Why is that okay?
Why is it okay that a former president don't got shit to say while we are descending into fascism?
Why is that okay with y'all?
He did his time.
This isn't a fucking jail.
Every president should be out here loud.
Every president that is alive should be out here loud, whether it is Barack Obama, Bill Clinton, every president, every member of the fucking cabinets.
All of them should be out here loud, kind of fucking Lisa.
All of them.
But they're not because they're complicit.
You're damn rude, eh?
You're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn